MIRCEA-DUMITRU DUCA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



Hard Skills















HTML5



Self Definition

github.com/BorisForis

mircea-97a951192/

+40770299096

mircealike2013@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/duca-

Contact

I am a hard-working individual who strives always to learn more. My experience as a Game Tester has offered me the premises to develop some important soft skills: attention to detail - which I consider a valuable skill for a software developer; empathy - the ability to see a project from the user perspective; big picture thinking - the ability to understand the entire project even I am just a part of it; time and task management - the ability to understand the priorities of a project and to meet the deadlines. Also, I must mention that I am a team player, even though I can work independently.

Strength

I am good at algorithms, logic and writing efficient code. I can easily learn new concepts and apply them almost immediately as I learn them. I can come up with good ideas for solving most problems, issues and situations. I am also someone that can easily get along with others and work as a team. Am good at presentations and on the spot thinking when something may not work the way it was intended. I have a good understanding of both frontend and backend.

Recent Projects

PLAYERREVIEWEDGAMES

https://github.com/happy-qa/frontend

A site for reviewing games honestly and getting game news. I have primarily worked on Frontend, created with Vite React, and styled with Tailwind CSS, Using ESLint to ensure a clean work environment and prettify for cleaner code.

ANIME CAULDRON

https://github.com/BorisForis/Anime-Cauldron

A small site where people can log in, search for, review and rate anime but also get random anime recommendations based on certain criteria. Frontend created with Vite react, and styled with Tailwind CSS. Using ESLint to ensure a clean working environment, and prettify for cleaner code. The backend was created using Java Spring, Spring Security and SupaBase as the database.

EMPLOYEE MADNESS

https://github.com/BorisForis/Employee-Madness

It is a website where you can manage employee data for a company, allowing a wide variety of operations on its database. I have primarily worked on Frontend using React, and CSS for styling.

Work Experience

Cashier (2022 - 2023) — Boss MiniBurgers Customer Service Representative (2021 - 2022) — CGS Romania Game Tester (2019 - 2021) — Ubisoft

Education

Full Stack Developer (2023 - 2023) — Codecool Academy Baccalaureate Degree (2015 - 2019) — CT.A.L.P I.N. Socolescu

Spoken Languages

English — Advanced